[
{
   "id": 1,
  "level": "A2",
  "skill": "reading",
  "passage": "Last weekend, Tom and his friends decided to go camping in the mountains. They planned everything carefully. On Saturday morning, they packed their bags and left the city early. The journey took about three hours.\n\nWhen they arrived, the weather was sunny and warm. They set up their tents near a small lake, and after that, they went hiking. The view from the top of the mountain was amazing! They took many photos and enjoyed the fresh air.\n\nIn the evening, they made a fire, cooked sausages, and told funny stories. They didn’t have mobile signal, so nobody used their phones. That made the experience even better.\n\nAt night, it got very cold. Tom couldn’t sleep well because he forgot his sleeping bag. The others shared their blankets with him.\n\nOn Sunday morning, it started to rain, so they packed up and returned home. Although the trip wasn’t perfect, Tom said it was one of the best weekends of his life.",
   "question": "Where did Tom and his friends go last weekend?",
   "options": ["To the beach", "To the mountains", "To the forest", "To a village"],
   "answer": "To the mountains"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "level": "A2",
  "skill": "reading",
  "passage": "Last weekend, Tom and his friends decided to go camping in the mountains. They planned everything carefully. On Saturday morning, they packed their bags and left the city early. The journey took about three hours.\n\nWhen they arrived, the weather was sunny and warm. They set up their tents near a small lake, and after that, they went hiking. The view from the top of the mountain was amazing! They took many photos and enjoyed the fresh air.\n\nIn the evening, they made a fire, cooked sausages, and told funny stories. They didn’t have mobile signal, so nobody used their phones. That made the experience even better.\n\nAt night, it got very cold. Tom couldn’t sleep well because he forgot his sleeping bag. The others shared their blankets with him.\n\nOn Sunday morning, it started to rain, so they packed up and returned home. Although the trip wasn’t perfect, Tom said it was one of the best weekends of his life.",
      "question": "How long did the journey take?",
      "options": ["Two hours", "Four hours", "Three hours", "One hour"],
      "answer": "Three hours"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "level": "A2",
  "skill": "reading",
  "passage": "Last weekend, Tom and his friends decided to go camping in the mountains. They planned everything carefully. On Saturday morning, they packed their bags and left the city early. The journey took about three hours.\n\nWhen they arrived, the weather was sunny and warm. They set up their tents near a small lake, and after that, they went hiking. The view from the top of the mountain was amazing! They took many photos and enjoyed the fresh air.\n\nIn the evening, they made a fire, cooked sausages, and told funny stories. They didn’t have mobile signal, so nobody used their phones. That made the experience even better.\n\nAt night, it got very cold. Tom couldn’t sleep well because he forgot his sleeping bag. The others shared their blankets with him.\n\nOn Sunday morning, it started to rain, so they packed up and returned home. Although the trip wasn’t perfect, Tom said it was one of the best weekends of his life.",
  


      "question": "What did they do after setting up the tents?",
      "options": ["Went swimming", "Cooked food", "Went hiking", "Took a nap"],
      "answer": "Went hiking"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "level": "A2",
  "skill": "reading",
  "passage": "Last weekend, Tom and his friends decided to go camping in the mountains. They planned everything carefully. On Saturday morning, they packed their bags and left the city early. The journey took about three hours.\n\nWhen they arrived, the weather was sunny and warm. They set up their tents near a small lake, and after that, they went hiking. The view from the top of the mountain was amazing! They took many photos and enjoyed the fresh air.\n\nIn the evening, they made a fire, cooked sausages, and told funny stories. They didn’t have mobile signal, so nobody used their phones. That made the experience even better.\n\nAt night, it got very cold. Tom couldn’t sleep well because he forgot his sleeping bag. The others shared their blankets with him.\n\nOn Sunday morning, it started to rain, so they packed up and returned home. Although the trip wasn’t perfect, Tom said it was one of the best weekends of his life.",
  


      "question": "Why didn’t they use their phones?",
      "options": ["They were broken", "They had no signal", "They were charging", "They lost them"],
      "answer": "They had no signal"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "level": "A2",
  "skill": "reading",
  "passage": "Last weekend, Tom and his friends decided to go camping in the mountains. They planned everything carefully. On Saturday morning, they packed their bags and left the city early. The journey took about three hours.\n\nWhen they arrived, the weather was sunny and warm. They set up their tents near a small lake, and after that, they went hiking. The view from the top of the mountain was amazing! They took many photos and enjoyed the fresh air.\n\nIn the evening, they made a fire, cooked sausages, and told funny stories. They didn’t have mobile signal, so nobody used their phones. That made the experience even better.\n\nAt night, it got very cold. Tom couldn’t sleep well because he forgot his sleeping bag. The others shared their blankets with him.\n\nOn Sunday morning, it started to rain, so they packed up and returned home. Although the trip wasn’t perfect, Tom said it was one of the best weekends of his life.",
  


      "question": "Why couldn’t Tom sleep well?",
      "options": ["It was too noisy", "He wasn’t tired", "He forgot his sleeping bag", "His tent was broken"],
      "answer": "He forgot his sleeping bag"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "level": "A2",
  "skill": "reading",
  "passage": "Last weekend, Tom and his friends decided to go camping in the mountains. They planned everything carefully. On Saturday morning, they packed their bags and left the city early. The journey took about three hours.\n\nWhen they arrived, the weather was sunny and warm. They set up their tents near a small lake, and after that, they went hiking. The view from the top of the mountain was amazing! They took many photos and enjoyed the fresh air.\n\nIn the evening, they made a fire, cooked sausages, and told funny stories. They didn’t have mobile signal, so nobody used their phones. That made the experience even better.\n\nAt night, it got very cold. Tom couldn’t sleep well because he forgot his sleeping bag. The others shared their blankets with him.\n\nOn Sunday morning, it started to rain, so they packed up and returned home. Although the trip wasn’t perfect, Tom said it was one of the best weekends of his life.",
  


      "question": "What did the others do to help Tom at night?",
      "options": ["Gave him a sleeping bag", "Shared their blankets", "Made a fire", "Moved him indoors"],
      "answer": "Shared their blankets"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "level": "A2",
  "skill": "reading",
  "passage": "Last weekend, Tom and his friends decided to go camping in the mountains. They planned everything carefully. On Saturday morning, they packed their bags and left the city early. The journey took about three hours.\n\nWhen they arrived, the weather was sunny and warm. They set up their tents near a small lake, and after that, they went hiking. The view from the top of the mountain was amazing! They took many photos and enjoyed the fresh air.\n\nIn the evening, they made a fire, cooked sausages, and told funny stories. They didn’t have mobile signal, so nobody used their phones. That made the experience even better.\n\nAt night, it got very cold. Tom couldn’t sleep well because he forgot his sleeping bag. The others shared their blankets with him.\n\nOn Sunday morning, it started to rain, so they packed up and returned home. Although the trip wasn’t perfect, Tom said it was one of the best weekends of his life.",
  


      "question": "What was the weather like when they arrived?",
      "options": ["Rainy and cold", "Sunny and warm", "Windy", "Snowy"],
      "answer": "Sunny and warm"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "level": "A2",
  "skill": "reading",
  "passage": "Last weekend, Tom and his friends decided to go camping in the mountains. They planned everything carefully. On Saturday morning, they packed their bags and left the city early. The journey took about three hours.\n\nWhen they arrived, the weather was sunny and warm. They set up their tents near a small lake, and after that, they went hiking. The view from the top of the mountain was amazing! They took many photos and enjoyed the fresh air.\n\nIn the evening, they made a fire, cooked sausages, and told funny stories. They didn’t have mobile signal, so nobody used their phones. That made the experience even better.\n\nAt night, it got very cold. Tom couldn’t sleep well because he forgot his sleeping bag. The others shared their blankets with him.\n\nOn Sunday morning, it started to rain, so they packed up and returned home. Although the trip wasn’t perfect, Tom said it was one of the best weekends of his life.",
  


      "question": "What happened on Sunday morning?",
      "options": ["They went hiking", "They visited another place", "It started to rain", "They got lost"],
      "answer": "It started to rain"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "level": "A2",
  "skill": "reading",
  "passage": "Last weekend, Tom and his friends decided to go camping in the mountains. They planned everything carefully. On Saturday morning, they packed their bags and left the city early. The journey took about three hours.\n\nWhen they arrived, the weather was sunny and warm. They set up their tents near a small lake, and after that, they went hiking. The view from the top of the mountain was amazing! They took many photos and enjoyed the fresh air.\n\nIn the evening, they made a fire, cooked sausages, and told funny stories. They didn’t have mobile signal, so nobody used their phones. That made the experience even better.\n\nAt night, it got very cold. Tom couldn’t sleep well because he forgot his sleeping bag. The others shared their blankets with him.\n\nOn Sunday morning, it started to rain, so they packed up and returned home. Although the trip wasn’t perfect, Tom said it was one of the best weekends of his life.",
  


      "question": "What does the text suggest about not using phones?",
      "options": ["It made the trip worse", "It didn’t matter", "It made the experience better", "It caused problems"],
      "answer": "It made the experience better"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "level": "A2",
  "skill": "reading",
  "passage": "Last weekend, Tom and his friends decided to go camping in the mountains. They planned everything carefully. On Saturday morning, they packed their bags and left the city early. The journey took about three hours.\n\nWhen they arrived, the weather was sunny and warm. They set up their tents near a small lake, and after that, they went hiking. The view from the top of the mountain was amazing! They took many photos and enjoyed the fresh air.\n\nIn the evening, they made a fire, cooked sausages, and told funny stories. They didn’t have mobile signal, so nobody used their phones. That made the experience even better.\n\nAt night, it got very cold. Tom couldn’t sleep well because he forgot his sleeping bag. The others shared their blankets with him.\n\nOn Sunday morning, it started to rain, so they packed up and returned home. Although the trip wasn’t perfect, Tom said it was one of the best weekends of his life.",
  


      "question": "How did Tom feel about the trip in the end?",
      "options": ["It was boring", "It was one of the best weekends", "It was a disaster", "It was okay"],
      "answer": "It was one of the best weekends"
    }
  ]

